So hey gas welcome back to this video and
today we are going to talk
about an accidental scooter which is
Activa 125 bs6 model so it met with an
accident due to touching a bike
because he was going from one side and not
from the other side and due to negligence the scooter and bike met with an
accident now after this when the
customer comes here then first of all the insurance of this vehicle is required
then after that he needs
all the papers of the vehicle then the license of the person who was driving the vehicle
and then after that the process was taken forward
then almost all the work is
over now so basically I am shooting this video
only after all the work is over so right
now its proximity cost is
around 20000 which the customer will have to pay approximately 20% of it
so that will come to
around 4000 or it can be under that also it will
not be much so let's watch this video
completely to make an
insurance claim for which the front left
side will be covered
how many parts are there
[Music]
[music]
say something
[music] let's
make it
6:00